{
    "id": "8f52c040507b446899f7e6187c86c4a7",
    "title": "Despite, In Spite Of, However, Although",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We went out ....................... the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in spite",
                "in spite of",
                "despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dae99bb0ffc34d90b1eefb3fe63b4353"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went on working ……………….. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in spite of",
                "although",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63d8048447024781ace35bade9d3fa9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went to work ………………… the fact that it was a holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "in spite of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "92359f71c327418d8f61d56a79fc7c6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. she didn’t like the cutlet, I enjoyed it very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a75fc01cf7e1412b9cb70ec69276ac07"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had invited him ………………….., he didn’t come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "though",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b2ed98fff4d45438367b82cd88f4ca9"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was fun, ………………… dangerous.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7bbfe85b29443e58d076b85c16ba742"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late ………………. everybody else was on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "despite",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "106f5c21b5054542abbe27be209148f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I was late, everybody else was on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "185ccc259f4840b2b2c0392adf3fabb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "They managed to do it, ………………….. I was not there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "although",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0222b8b944740909adca8d988e53ca2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went ………………… I had not been invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "although",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0a24233c9ac4560bd368c58b59d2d0b"
        }
    ]
}